{"Answer": "Effect of Rosiglitazone on the Risk of Myocardial Infarction and Death from Cardiovascular Causes\n\nRosiglitazone is widely used to treat patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus , but its effect on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality has not been determined .\n\nWe conducted searches of the published literature , the Web site of the Food and Drug Administration , and a clinical-trials registry maintained by the drug manufacturer ( GlaxoSmithKline ) . Criteria for inclusion in our meta-analysis included a study duration of more than 24 weeks , the use of a randomized control group not receiving rosiglitazone , and the availability of outcome data for myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes . Of 116 potentially relevant studies , 42 trials met the inclusion criteria . We tabulated all occurrences of myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes .\n\nData were combined by means of a fixed-effects model . In the 42 trials , the mean age of the subjects was approximately 56 years , and the mean baseline glycated hemoglobin level was approximately 8.2 % . In the rosiglitazone group , as compared with the control group , the odds ratio for myocardial infarction was 1.43 ( 95 % confidence interval ( CI ) , 1.03 to 1.98 ; P = 0.03 ) , and the odds ratio for death from cardiovascular causes was 1.64 ( 95 % CI , 0.98 to 2.74 ; P = 0.06 ) .\n\nRosiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and with an increase in the risk of death from cardiovascular causes that had borderline significance . Our study was limited by a lack of access to original source data , which would have enabled time-to-event analysis . Despite these limitations , patients and providers should consider the potential for serious adverse cardiovascular effects of treatment with rosiglitazone for type 2 diabetes .\n\n", "Topic": "cardio", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "1.43": ["Outcomes"], "1.64": ["Outcomes"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "56 year": ["Age"], "1.43": ["Effect-strength"], "1.64": ["Effect-strength"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": [], "Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": [], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Age": "The mean age of the subjects was of 56 years.", "Condition": "Patients had type 2 diabetes mellitus.", "Sample-size": "42 trials were analyzed in this study.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the effect of Rosiglitazone.", "Duration": "Studies included in the analysis lasted for more than 24 weeks.", "Control": "Studies included in the analysis had a control group not receiving rosiglitazone.", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured the myocardial infarction and deaths from cardiovascular causes.", "Effect-strength": "In the rosiglitazone group, as compared with the control group, the odds ratio of myocardial infarction was 1.43, and for death  from cardiovascular causes it was 1.64.", "Conclusion-general": "Rosiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction, and of death from cardiovascular causes."}, "id": "NEJMoa072761", "children": [{"Answer": "Effect of Rosiglitazone on myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes risk. We did searches of published literature from the Food and Drug administration as well as a clinical-trails registry maintained by the drug manufacturer GlaxoSmithKline. Only studies of more than 24 weeks, using a randomized control group not taking rosiglitazone, and has outcome date for myocardia infarction and death from cardiovascular causes. Of 116 potentially relevant studies, 42 trials met the inclusion criteria. All occurences of myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes were counted and sorted. In these trials the mean age of the subjects were approximately 56 years, and the mean baseline glycated hemoglobin level was approximately 8.2%. Rosignlitazone was associated with a large increase in risk of myocardial infarction as well as an increased risk of death from cardiovascular causes.", "AssignmentId": "3SB4CE2TJWG9RVB969CZL9QH9EUAXF", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "56 year": ["Age"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3SB4CE2TJWG9RVB969CZL9QH9EUAXF", "children": [{"Answer": "A meta-analysis was done on Rosiglitazone to determine its effects on the risk of myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes. This drug is used to treat patients with type 2 diabetes. 116 potential studies were found and collected, but only 42 of them met the criteria needed for inclusion. It was found that Rosiglitazone was associated with a large increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes. Although the study was limited, both patients and providers should consider the drug's effects.", "AssignmentId": "3X4JMASXCNU6DFAQ9BNO76NCIQSB0H", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A34RU3V8G203GN", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3X4JMASXCNU6DFAQ9BNO76NCIQSB0H", "children": [{"Answer": "A study conducted on risk effects of Rosiglitazone on patients with type II diabetes and heart attack deaths.  However, the study was limited by a lack of accces to original data. In conclusion, patients and providers should consider adverse effects from rosiglitazone.", "AssignmentId": "3S0TNUHWKU3HA1DDIBR9VBHU4IID8X", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AAN06KVDS2XRY", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3S0TNUHWKU3HA1DDIBR9VBHU4IID8X", "children": [{"Answer": "Tests of the drug Rosiglitazone showed it was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and death. ", "AssignmentId": "3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF21H5G9Q", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1LMDMSKQ96PHP", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3D4CH1LGEBEK0Q6EPTYV1SF21H5G9Q", "children": [{"Answer": "The diabetes drug rosiglitazone increases risk of cardiovascular problems.", "AssignmentId": "3X87C8JFV7WTIUWR1V3YC1OUZS6QS9", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3X87C8JFV7WTIUWR1V3YC1OUZS6QS9"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "hiazolidinedione drugs are widely used to lower blood glucose levels in patients wit the type of 2 diabetes mellitus introglitazone , which was removed from the market because of hepatoxicity  , and two currently available agents, rosiglitazone and pioglitazone the thiazolidinediones are agonists for peroxisome-profiiferator-activated nuclear receptor are ligand-activated nuclear transcription factors the modulate gen expression,lowering blood glucose primarily by increasing insulin sensitivity in peripheral tissues rosiglitazone was introduced in 1999 and is widely used used as monotherapy or fixed dose combinations with either mertformin the original approval of rosiglitazone was based on the ability  of the drug to reduce blood glucose and glycated hemoglobin levels intial studies were not adequately powered to do determine the effects of the agent on micro vascular complications diabetes, including cardiovascular morbidity and morality however, the effect of any anti diabetic therapy on cardiovascular outcomes is particularly important because more than 65% of deaths in patients", "AssignmentId": "3Y4W8Q93L05FLD9QQ42JNP12E6KDVI", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AIV02RLU34H13", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3Y4W8Q93L05FLD9QQ42JNP12E6KDVI", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone has wide-spread use to treat patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus. Its effect on cardiovascular mobidity and mortality, however, has yet to be determined. After trials using a control group that did not receive rosiglitazone and one that did, it was determined that those that did take rosiglitazone had a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and increase in the risk of a death from cardiovascular causes. The findings indicate that patients and providers should consider the adverse effects.", "AssignmentId": "374TNBHA8CGQEG8001VNUNCVG4KQYN", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AJITIN95JSBAR", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "control group": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "control group": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_374TNBHA8CGQEG8001VNUNCVG4KQYN", "children": [{"Answer": "42 trials meeting inclusion criteria in subjects approx. 56 years old showed Rosiglitazone (a medication used to treat patients with Type II DM) was associated with an increased risk of myocardial infarction &amp; an increase risk of death from cardiovascular causes.", "AssignmentId": "39K0FND3AI0YXJC5S2AQASAJ3K8MAQ", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "56 year": ["Age"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["B"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_39K0FND3AI0YXJC5S2AQASAJ3K8MAQ", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone, a drug for treatment of type 2 diabetes ,has the potential for serious adverse cardiovascular effects. ", "AssignmentId": "358010RM5FETJJE7H43VHW4UVZMXVH", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_358010RM5FETJJE7H43VHW4UVZMXVH", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone has significant increase in risk of myocardial infarction.", "AssignmentId": "32VNZTT0A8PASA9GO9WGJOITHYH4RT", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1KR3HNLXSLC10", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_32VNZTT0A8PASA9GO9WGJOITHYH4RT"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Rosiglitzone is widely used to treat patients with type II DM, but its effect on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality has not been determined. A study was conducted of searches of published literature, the website of the FDA and a clinical trial registry maintained by GiaxoSmithKline. Criteria for inclusion in the meta-analysis included a study duration of more than 24 weeks, the use of randomized control group not receiving rosiglitazone, and the availability of outcome data for MI and death from cardiovascular causes. Of 116 potentially relevant studies, 42 trials met the inclusion criteria. Rosiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and with an increase in the risk of death from cardiovascular causes that had borderline significance. The study was limited by lack of access to original source data, which would have enabled time-to-event analysis. Despite limitations, patients and providers should consider the potential for serious adverse cardiovascular effects of treatment with rosiglitazone for Type 2 diabetes.", "AssignmentId": "3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6P0TZ5X", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6P0TZ5X", "children": [{"Answer": "With data analysis, it was determined that Rosiglitazone (widely used for treatment of patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus) was associated with a significant increase in the risk for myocardial infarction and with an increase  in the risk of death from cardiovascular causes that had borderline significance. Despite some study limitations, patients and providers should consider the potential for serious adverse cardiovascular effects of treatment with Rosiglitazone for type 2 diabetes.", "AssignmentId": "3QAPZX2QN5YCP2AUQIUD6DK8OLY02P", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3QAPZX2QN5YCP2AUQIUD6DK8OLY02P", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone, a type 2 diabetes drug, was studied by including 42 trials that met the study inclusion criteria. The study tested the drugs effect on both myocardial infarction and myocardial events. Rosiglitazone was associated with a significant increased risk of both. ", "AssignmentId": "3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA0FK1G5C", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "APHMJQQFW0U5S", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA0FK1G5C", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is associated with an increased risk of myocardial infarction &amp; increase risk of death from cardiovascular causes.", "AssignmentId": "3HMVI3QICKD2XCOJFM58TM4N8181Y1", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3HMVI3QICKD2XCOJFM58TM4N8181Y1", "children": [{"Answer": "There is potential for adverse CV effects with Rosiglitazone for type 2 DM.", "AssignmentId": "308XBLVESJPUD9UP3O63R2OZRR8BRI", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_308XBLVESJPUD9UP3O63R2OZRR8BRI"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "116 people were chosen as being potentially relevant for the study but only 42 met the inclusion critera which was a study of more then 24 weeks, the use of a randomized control group not receiving rosiglitazone and the availability of outcome data for myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular causes.All occurrences of myocardial and infarction and death from cardiovascular causes were tabulated. In the 42 trials the mean age was approximately 56 years old and the baseline glycated hemoglobin level was 8.2%. The rosiglitazone grup as compared to the control group the odds ratio for mycardio infarction was 1.43 and the odds ratio for death from cardiovascular causes was 1.64. Rosiglilazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and with an increase in the risk of death from cardiovascular causes that had borderline significance. Despite limitations the serious adverse effects of treatment with rosiglitazone for type 2 diabetes should be considered. ", "AssignmentId": "3Z7VU45IPZ2222YOB87R7TDPDKN1ZG", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A2YUCJ28XANFOX", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "1.43": ["Outcomes"], "1.64": ["Outcomes"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "56 year": ["Age"], "1.43": ["Effect-strength"], "1.64": ["Effect-strength"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3Z7VU45IPZ2222YOB87R7TDPDKN1ZG", "children": [{"Answer": "Type 2 diabetes patients are frequently treated with rosiglitazone.  A meta-analysis was performed to determine its effect on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality.  The combined data from 42 completed controlled trials with relevant adverse effect information were evaluated.  Treatment with rosiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction.  The increased risk of death from cardiovascular causes had borderline statistical significance.", "AssignmentId": "3VFJCI1K40KQ4Q20JAYHSDFW71XRG6", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A11DLGQTOOSIWR", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3VFJCI1K40KQ4Q20JAYHSDFW71XRG6", "children": [{"Answer": "A study found the effects of rosiglitazone on the risk of myocardial infarction and cardiovascular casued death. Rosiglitazone was associated with a large jump in risk of myocardial infarction and risk of death from cardiovascular causes that had borderline significance.", "AssignmentId": "3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6QAW5ZR", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3M0NZ3JDP2J1QKZ7CV93AJQ6QAW5ZR", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is popularly used to treat type 2 diabetes mellitus, but its effect on cardiovascular morbidity is undetermined.  ", "AssignmentId": "32UTUBMZ7HHM6GB6C8BDSZD2CW3VBB", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A3MT4SBSBPER68", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["C", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_32UTUBMZ7HHM6GB6C8BDSZD2CW3VBB", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is used despite the risk on mortality.", "AssignmentId": "3FTYUGLFSV6YNJUBKDK6JR732WMD58", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3FTYUGLFSV6YNJUBKDK6JR732WMD58"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "There is a medication called Rosiglitazone that is used to treat people who have type two diabetes mellitus. The effect it has on death or possible death by cardiovascular reasons is not defined. We made an attempt to find material from several sources to find out if there were any associated risk. The sources were various published literature, web site of the food and drug administration, and a registry of clinical trials by the manufacturer named GlaxoSmithKline. We established certain criteria the found material had to meet. The criteria included overall time of the study and use of a control group. Out of the 116 relevant studies only 42 met the standard set. The mean of all the data was used to establish the information to be used. The average age of those in the studies was 56 years old.The drug Rosiglitazone had a close link with a large increase in myocardial infarction and risk of death by cardiovascular reasons.", "AssignmentId": "3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP90NH2Q", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A39GH5GG2B7KA1", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "control group": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "56 year": ["Age"], "control group": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP90NH2Q", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is used to treat type2 diabetes. To study its effect on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality, of 116 potentially relevant studies, the data of 42 trials were included. The mean age was 56 years for the 42 studies and death by cardiovascular causes had a 1.64 ratio.&#13;Rosiglitazone was associated with a increased risk of myocardial infarction and increased risk of death from cardiovascular causes. The study had limited access to original source data, but still, patients should consider the potential side effects of rosiglitazone.", "AssignmentId": "3SNVL38CI5DR0A90R4T11A83EHCKCX", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AISNLDPD2DFEG", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "1.64": ["Outcomes"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "56 year": ["Age"], "1.64": ["Effect-strength"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3SNVL38CI5DR0A90R4T11A83EHCKCX", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazones effects on cardiovascular morbidity and death hasn't been determined. Patients and providers should consider the risk for serious harmful cardiovascular effects of treatment with rosiglitazone for individuals with type 2 diabetes. ", "AssignmentId": "340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q1HUUVB", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A3MT4SBSBPER68", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_340UGXU9DZM12FKCCZS8XP5Q1HUUVB", "children": [{"Answer": "Diabetes patients are at a significant risk of cardiovascular problems and death due to use of the drug rosiglitazone.", "AssignmentId": "3R9WASFE201TSHSWI7MCWVHJF52ZFY", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A6CVN7CSC1K26", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3R9WASFE201TSHSWI7MCWVHJF52ZFY", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone ups risk of myocardial infarction and cardiovascular deaths.", "AssignmentId": "358UUM7WR0O7BXRZQ7UNM02383Y7RD", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_358UUM7WR0O7BXRZQ7UNM02383Y7RD"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is a popular Type 2 Diabetes medication, but has not been tested for cardiovascular side effects. A meta-analysis was conducted on this subject. 116 studies were examined, and 42 met the criteria for the study: study duration of 24 or more weeks, use of a randomized control group that did not recieve the medication, and availability of myocardial infarction and cardiovascular death data. The average age of the patients in the studies was 56 years old, and the average baseline glycated hemoglobin level was 8.2%. The risk of both myocardial infarction and death from cardiovascular disease in the rosiglitazone group was higher than that of the control group. The studies showed that rosiglitazone was associated with significantly higher rates of myocaridal infarction. It was also associated with cardiovascular death, but this association was only borderline significant. The study could have been improved with better access to original source data, but still suggests that cardiovascular effects should be considered in patients taking rosiglitazone.", "AssignmentId": "3LJ7UR74RIYPDCHOV2FZA4DJGR34NW", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A3QFXP9WDS19PR", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "control group": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "56 year": ["Age"], "control group": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3LJ7UR74RIYPDCHOV2FZA4DJGR34NW", "children": [{"Answer": "Searches were conducted of published literature, the website of the FDA &amp; a clinical trials registry maintained by GlaxoSmithKline. Criteria for inclusion in the analysis included a study duration of &gt;24 weeks, the use of a random control group not receiving rosiglitazone &amp; the availability of outcome data for myocardial infarction &amp; death from cardiovascular causes. 42/116 trials met the inclusion criteria. Resiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of MI &amp; an increase in the risk of death from cardiovascular causes", "AssignmentId": "35GMH2SV3F2PNZETLNRPYFPFJYYOED", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A98E8M4QLI9RS", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_35GMH2SV3F2PNZETLNRPYFPFJYYOED", "children": [{"Answer": "In a recent meta analysis, results show that patients and providers should be cautious with the use of Rosiglitazone in the treatment of type 2 diabetes. Rosiglitazone was associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and cardiovascular death. ", "AssignmentId": "3FPRZHYEPZSH3L7TXFW7AGFQO4A3VC", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AON59V5VZU2AK", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3FPRZHYEPZSH3L7TXFW7AGFQO4A3VC", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone has a significant increase in risk of myocardial infarction and increase in risk of death from cardiovascular causes.", "AssignmentId": "3X73LLYYQ2ZJPO5JA9ZI4TMNL6BNH7", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1KR3HNLXSLC10", "Qualification": 0.6153846153846154, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3X73LLYYQ2ZJPO5JA9ZI4TMNL6BNH7", "children": [{"Answer": "The DM drug, Rosiglitazone was found to raise cardiovascular caused deaths.", "AssignmentId": "337RC3OW06NYJPXI3L076297OZ0LVP", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A37CE37LHUN8M6", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "60+", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_337RC3OW06NYJPXI3L076297OZ0LVP"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "We conducted searches of the published literature, the web site of the food and drug administration, and a clinical-trails registry maintained by the drug manufacturer. criteria for inclusion in our meta-analysis included a study duration of more than 24 weeks , the use of a randomized control group not receiving rosiglitazone, and the availability of outcome data for myocardial infraction and death from cardiovascular causes.we tabulated all occurrences of myocardial infraction and death from cardiovascular causes. data were combined by means of a fixed-effects model. In the 42 trials the mean age of the subjects was approximately 56 years, and the mean baseline glycated hemoglobin level was approximately 8.2%. In the rosiglitazone group, as compared with the control group, the odds ratio for myocardial infraction was 1.43, and the odds ratio for death from cardiovascular causes was 1.64.", "AssignmentId": "3S06PH7KSSPZZ1TSJQIUG1UMQ3XD1G", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A3F6TS7I3CSUM8", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "56 year": ["Participants"], "1.43": ["Outcomes"], "1.64": ["Outcomes"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"], "42 trial": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "56 year": ["Age"], "1.43": ["Effect-strength"], "1.64": ["Effect-strength"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"], "42 trial": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["A"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3S06PH7KSSPZZ1TSJQIUG1UMQ3XD1G", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone has been popularly used to treat patients that have type 2 diabetes mellitus, but the effect it has on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality hasn't been proven yet. The data from research and clinical trials confirmed that rosiglitazone had an increase effect in the risk of myocardial infarction and also an increase risk of death from cardiovascular causes. The original source data was unable to be accessed, but patients and providers should take into account the serious cardiovascular effects rosiglitazone has on it's patients.", "AssignmentId": "3GD6L00D3TI23VZ5WJHXZRHGZPP1M2", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A3MT4SBSBPER68", "Qualification": 0.8461538461538461, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3GD6L00D3TI23VZ5WJHXZRHGZPP1M2", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is a drug for diabetes, but it hasn't been studied for death. Previous studies were researched for answers. Rosiglitazone was found to increase the risk of heart attack (myocardial infarction). It was also fond to increase the risk of cardiac disease.", "AssignmentId": "39ZSFO5CA9HSBKKIVAEPU1UW6UXJUP", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AHYXP6QIMYJLD", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_39ZSFO5CA9HSBKKIVAEPU1UW6UXJUP", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone was associated with a big increase in the risk of myocardial infarction and with type 2 diabetes mellitus.", "AssignmentId": "38F5OAUN5OXUM3DWU2IT8W0XLR4H7O", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_38F5OAUN5OXUM3DWU2IT8W0XLR4H7O", "children": [{"Answer": "The drug Rosiglitazone can negatively affect the heart in diabetics. ", "AssignmentId": "3SB5N7Y3O4P24WI1PXF28HE9YM7G0S", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "APRT9QD3FKFHQ", "Qualification": 0.7692307692307693, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["C", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["C", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["B"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["C"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3SB5N7Y3O4P24WI1PXF28HE9YM7G0S"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "The wide research about to treat patients with the type 2 diabetes. there is a lot of symptoms and chances when someone have diabetes to occur cardio attack.this study shows some randomized control not receiving rosiglitazone. and the availability included a study duration of more than 24 weeks,the use of the outcome data is very precious.and 116 potentially studies and 42 trails men the inclusion criteria. we tabulated all occurrences of myocardial infraction.data were combined by means of a fixed effects model. in the rosiglitazone group as compared with the control group.rosiglitazone was associated with a significance.our studywas limited by a lack of access to original source data and which has some kinds of despite these limitation,patients and providers should consider the potential for serious adverse cardiovascular effects of treatment with rosilitazone for type 2 diabetes.            ", "AssignmentId": "3B4YI393VAH5VAB4TZS3713VH6MSSB", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1RVRSK2GTUVGK", "Qualification": 0.46153846153846156, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "24 week": ["Intervention"], "control group": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "24 week": ["Duration"], "control group": ["Control"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Control": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3B4YI393VAH5VAB4TZS3713VH6MSSB", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone is a widely used drug to treat Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus but the drugs effects on cardiovascular morbidity and mortality has not yet been determined. Through meta-analysis of 42 published clinical trials and literature, Risiglitazone has been associated with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infraction (odds ratio = 1.43, 95% CI, 1.03 to 1.98; P = 0.03) with a risk of death from cardiovascular causes (odds ratio =1.64, 95% CI, 0.98 to 2.74; P= 0.06) that previously had borderline significance.  ", "AssignmentId": "3S3AMIZX3VQJM43QZN7EXXDDU8VDCT", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1DN8ZAIT1U3I8", "Qualification": 0.9230769230769231, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"], "diabete": ["Participants"], "1.43": ["Outcomes"], "1.64": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"], "diabete": ["Condition"], "1.43": ["Effect-strength"], "1.64": ["Effect-strength"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3S3AMIZX3VQJM43QZN7EXXDDU8VDCT", "children": [{"Answer": "This study was on the effect of Rosiglitazone when used to treat patients with type 2 diabetus mellitus. Rosiglitazone has been associated  with a significant increase in the risk of myocardial infarction with adverse effects.", "AssignmentId": "3A7Y0R2P2P9KSOED0FPCE8T00BVJXW", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A1AZV2XOQK7RSW", "Qualification": 0.6923076923076923, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3A7Y0R2P2P9KSOED0FPCE8T00BVJXW", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone increased risk of myocardial infarction and cardiovascular assoc. deaths according to a study with limited data.", "AssignmentId": "3W92K5RLWV2KH0UXBYK0PDDA23G5VP", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "A2ELH7YDLFNJUZ", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "myocardial infarction": ["Outcomes-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3W92K5RLWV2KH0UXBYK0PDDA23G5VP", "children": [{"Answer": "Rosiglitazone use increases risk of heart attack and other causes of death.", "AssignmentId": "3KIBXJ1WD6FS9Z63H92SWA2K374KOR", "Question": "NEJMoa072761", "WorkerId": "AVBRJBJONL47I", "Qualification": 1.0, "Topic": "cardio", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa072761", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention"], "death": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"rosiglitazone": ["Intervention-general"], "death": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A", "C"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Age": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Control": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa072761_3KIBXJ1WD6FS9Z63H92SWA2K374KOR"}]}]}]}]}]}